This is Mion.
（魅音(みおん)）魅音です
（魅音）分かりました
そちらの対応はお願いします
I understand.
Please handle the situation.
Also, be sure
everyone remains silent.
それから一切の口封じを
よろしくお願いします
ええでは…
Yes. Later.
（詩音(しおん)）な…なに？口封じって
What does
"remain silent" mean?
聞いてた？
Were you listening?
I, um, don't know
what you're talking about.
あっ…知ら…ハハッ…
何のことか分からない
（魅音）聞こえたとおりです
富竹(とみたけ)さんと鷹野(たかの)さんが―
It's exactly what you heard.
Tomitake-san and Takano-san
were cursed by Oyashiro-sama.
オヤシロさまのたたりに
遭われました
本当にお気の毒なことです
It's really unfortunate.
Sis, what are you...
お姉ハハッ…何を…
（魅音）富竹さんは
自らの手で喉をかきむしって―
Tomitake-san killed himself
by clawing at his own throat.
お亡くなりになりました
Takano-san was stuffed in a barrel
and burned deep in the mountains...
鷹野さんは遠くの山奥で
ドラム缶に詰められて―
焼き殺されたそうです
...apparently.
（詩音）な…なに？それ
なんでそんな死に方…
W-What's that?
Why'd they die that way?
Don't you understand, Shion?
理由なんて
ひとつしかないじゃないですか
There's only one reason.
な…何の理由かな？
W-What's that?
オヤシロさまのたたり…
Oyashiro-sama's curse.
Satoshi-kun, I finally understand.
（詩音）
悟史(さとし)君私やっと分かったよ
As I thought, everything was
done by the Sonozaki family.
やっぱり
全て園崎(そのざき)本家の仕業だってことが
悟史君の無念は
きっと私が晴らすから
I will definitely
take revenge for you.
私は
悟史君みたいに殺されないから！
I will not get killed like you.
Who was calling so late?
（お魎(りょう)）
こんな遅くに誰からの電話だんね？
- "Eye Opening" Chapter -
Episode 04: REVENGE
When They Cry
Behind where I looked back
(who's there in the front)?
I raised my nails in the dark
(and slashed the night).
Raindrops become droplets of
blood and drip down the throat.
If you don't have
a place to go back to...
...then stop here on my finger.
I'll take you away
along with that finger.
To the unopenable
forest where cicadas cry.
You can't turn back anymore.
（魅音）
詩音これは何のマネなの？
Shion?
What's the meaning of this?
You never imagined
you'd get locked up, huh?
まさか自分が閉じ込められるとは
思わなかった？
園崎家当主代行として命じます
ここを開けなさい
As the Sonozaki head's
representative, I order you.
Open this door.
アハハッ…
声にいまひとつすごみが欠けるね
Your voice is lacking power.
当主さまはもっと傲慢でなきゃ
The head should
be more arrogant.
But even if you
threatened me with violence...
…とはいえ
今のあんたがすごんでも―
滑稽なだけなんだけどね
...it'd just look comical.
鷹野さんをドラム缶に詰めて
焼き殺したってのは―
Stuffing Takano-san into a barrel
and burning her was impressive...
なかなかだけど
富竹さんのはなに？
...but what about Tomitake-san?
You pumped him
with weird drugs?
怪しい薬でも注射したの？
それともそういう死に方に
見せる拷問道具でもあるわけ？
Or is there some torture tool that
makes it seem he died that way?
H-How would I know?
わ…私が知るわけないでしょう
ねえ魅音反抗的な態度
取らないほうがいいと思うよ
Hey, Mion. You shouldn't
take on a rebellious attitude.
Since you've done it this far,
I can no longer stop myself.
ここまでやっちゃった以上
私も引っ込みがつかないんだから
Then I'll ask.
じゃ聞くよ
雛見沢(ひなみざわ)連続怪死事件…
Are Hinamizawa's
serial mysterious deaths...
...also known as
"Oyashiro-sama's curse"...
通称“オヤシロさまのたたり”
これってやっぱり
ダム戦争のけじめってやつ？
...responsible for the dam war?
私は多分そうだと思ってる
I think so.
（詩音）
次期当主さまが何を曖昧なことを…
How could the next
head be so vague?
The next head is nothing more
than Granny's spokesperson.
（魅音）次期当主なんて…
ばっちゃの取り次ぎにすぎないよ
じゃ
オヤシロさまのたたりってのは―
Then Oyashiro-sama's curse
is solely decided by Granny?
鬼ばばが
全部 独断で決めてるんだ？
ヤバイ話は
ばっちゃが１人で決めてる
Granny alone decides
the super-risky issues.
I'm just a public spokesperson...
私は
表向きの取り次ぎをしているだけで
...and I think there's another
person who does the rest.
影の部分を取り次いでいる別の
誰かがいると思う
But Tomitake-san and Takano-san
aren't tied to the dam war...
（詩音）
でも富竹さんと鷹野さんは―
ダム戦争に関係してないのに
なぜ犠牲に選ばれたの？
...so why were they sacrificed?
Is it because they snuck
into the ritual tool shrine?
やっぱり
祭具殿に忍び込んだから？
ハッ…祭具殿を侵したの？
They violated the shrine?
Oh? I thought you already knew.
ありゃ…知ってるとばかり…
If they did that, then it's a given.
（魅音）
そんなことしたら当然だよ
でもさ魅音
たたりで１人死んだら―
But, Mion, wasn't there a rule
that one dies from the curse...
１人いけにえになって消えるのが
ルールじゃなかったっけ？
...and another
vanishes as a sacrifice?
鷹野さんと富竹さんは
２人とも死んじゃってるんだけど
Takano-san and Tomitake-san
are both dead, you know.
自信はないけど―
I'm not too sure...
祭具殿に忍び込んだのは
実は４人とか…
...but could it be four people
really snuck into the shrine...
…でもう２人は―
...and the other two were
spirited away by the demon?
いけにえってことで
鬼隠しになってるんじゃないかな？
Could it be me and Kei-chan?
まさか私と圭(けい)ちゃん？
Hideous Granny,
won't you please wake up?
（詩音）鬼ばばさま そろそろ
目を覚ましてくださいません？
ひょっとして眠ったフリをして
やり過ごそうとか考えてません？
Don't tell me you're acting like
you're sleeping to avoid all this.
フン…
見えます？見えてない？
Can you see this? You can't?
She's dead.
死んじゃってるよチッ！
Damn.
マジか？
Are you serious?
何もしゃべらず
悟史君への謝罪もないまま…
Without saying a word and
without an apology to Satoshi-kun.
苦しみもせず死ぬなんて…
How can she die
without going through pain?
It's unforgivable!
許せない！
Have you learned
your lesson, hideous Granny?
思い知ったか鬼ばば！
もしかして…
Could it be...
あんたが
レナの言ってたオヤシロさま？
...that you're the Oyashiro-sama
Rena talked about?
Stupid! Who'd believe that?
バ～カ！誰が信じるかよええ？
Mion, one of our relatives
said a long time ago...
昔親戚の誰かが言ってたじゃん
この地下拷問室の
どこかに隠し井戸があって
...that there's a hidden well in
this underground torture room...
そこに
外へ出られる秘密の通路があるって
...and a secret path
that leads outside.
If you keep that attitude up...
あんたがそんな態度だと―
また
ムチで鬼ばばに聞くしかないけど
...I'll have to ask the hideous
granny again with the whip.
そ…そこの奥暗がりの牢屋(ろうや)の中
B-Beyond there, in that dark cell.
I see.
へえうまく隠したもんだね
They hid this well.
Have you gone
down here before?
魅音はこの中下りたことあるの？
I don't even want to.
下りたくもない
（詩音）アハハッ！そりゃそうだ
Of course...
...since it's said that corpses are
thrown out there after the torture.
拷問で殺された死体を
捨てるのに使ってるって話だもんね
S-Shion, are you planning
to let Granny fall?
（魅音）し…詩音！
ばっちゃを落とす気？
I'm not letting her fall.
落とすんじゃないよ捨てるんだよ
I'm throwing her away.
She's already dead.
もう死んでるしね
（魅音）ハッ…
アア…ひどい…
It's horrible.
詩音どうしてこんなことを？
Shion, how could
you do such a thing?
Who knows?
（詩音）さあね？
悟史？
Satoshi?
敵討ちってこと？
Are you taking revenge?
ねえ魅音こうして思い返すと―
Hey, Mion.
Now that I think back...
私はやっぱり鬼ばばを
殺すだけの理由があったと思うよ
...I think I had a reason
to kill the hideous granny.
Do you know why?
なぜか分かる？
It's not just because she's
the one behind Satoshi's murder.
単に悟史君を殺した
張本人だからってわけじゃないよ
It's because she lied.
それはウソをついたから
あんたも言ったよね？
“爪を剥がせば全て許す”って
You said it too, didn't you?
That if I tore off my nails,
all would be forgiven.
だから私は爪を剥がしたんだよ
３枚も！
That's why I tore off
my nails. Three of them.
That was supposed to be
my responsibility, right?
それでけじめってことに
なったんだよね？
ハッ…
（詩音）でも約束は守られなかった
But that promise wasn't kept.
Satoshi-kun was still erased.
悟史君は
やっぱり消されてしまった
Why?
What's the meaning of this?
どうして？どういうことなの？
あのとき…悟史君が
いなくなってしまったあと―
That time, after he vanished,
you came to me and said...
あんた 来て言ったよね？
“悟史君と私の関係は
もうけじめがついた”って
...that the responsibility for our
relationship had been settled.
そしてこうも言ったよね？
And you also said...
“悟史君の失踪の理由は
園崎本家は何も知らない”と
...the Sonozakis didn't know
anything about his disappearance.
- Y-Yeah, that's really...
- You lied!
う…うん本当に…
ウソだ！
Lied! Lied! Lied!
ウソだ！ウソだ！ウソだ！
Liar!
ウソつき！
（蹴る音）
Liar! Liar! Liar! Liar!
ウソつき！ ウソつき！ ウソつき！
ウソつきこの！この！この！
You! You! You!
返してよ悟史君！返してよ！
Give me back Satoshi-kun!
Give him back!
（蹴る音）
返して返して！
Give him back! Give him back!
返して！返して！
魅音
（魅音）ハッ…
Mion, sorry for frightening you.
怖がらせて ごめん
魅音が魅音の言うとおり
何も知らなかったなら―
If you really didn't know as
you said, then I won't torment you.
魅音はいじめないからね
安心して
Don't worry.
でももし
魅音もウソをついていたら―
But if you were also lying...
そのときはどういう目に
遭わされてもしかたないよね
...then it will no longer matter
what happens to you, right?
When They Cry
はい園崎です
Hello, Sonozaki residence.
（公由(きみよし)）朝早くにすみませんな
公由でございます
Sorry to call you so early.
This is Kimiyoshi.
おばあちゃんは
まだお休みですかな？
Is your grandmother
still sleeping?
Yes, it seems she's
tired from yesterday.
はい昨日のがこたえたみたいです
しばらく寝かせておこうかと
思います
I'm letting her rest awhile.
Then could you place
a message next to her pillow?
じゃ枕元に
伝言を置いてもらっていいかな？
はい
Yes.
えっとね昨日の件で至急に
役員会を開くことになったんだけど
Let's see, regarding yesterday,
could you tell her we set...
それをね今日の夕方５時から―
...an emergency meeting at five
in the shrine assembly room?
神社の集会所でって
伝えてもらえる？
分かりました伝えておきます
I understand. I'll tell her.
はい園崎です
Sonozaki residence.
Mion-san?
Good morning, this is Kasai.
（葛西(かさい)）魅音さんですか？
おはようございます葛西です
あっ葛西…さんですか
おはようございます
Kasai-san? Good morning.
Is Shion-san still there?
詩音さんはまだ
そちらにいらっしゃいますか？
Shion is just washing her face.
詩音はさっき顔を洗ってました
呼んできますね
I'll get her.
（詩音）葛西？おはようです
Kasai? Good morning!
Good morning, Shion-san.
（葛西）
おはようございます詩音さん
Do you have a way
to return to Okinomiya?
興宮(おきのみや)へ帰る足はありますか？
う～ん…なんとかなるから大丈夫
I'll manage, so don't worry.
Anyway, have you heard?
それより葛西聞いてる？
（葛西）何をでしょう？
Heard what?
ゆうべの犠牲者の２人がどうして
オヤシロさまのたたりを受けたか？
Why the two sacrifices last night
were cursed by Oyashiro-sama.
いいえ
No.
実は
ゆうべちょっと聞いた話だと…
Well, from what
I heard last night...
...it seems they picked the lock
and snuck into the ritual tool shrine.
祭具殿に忍び込んだらしいのよ
南京錠を開けて
How foolish.
バカなことを…
（詩音）でさ実はさ…
To tell you the truth...
I was there too.
私もなんだけど…
（葛西）入ったんですか？
You went in?
うんその…鷹野さんに誘われてさ
I was invited in by Takano-san.
鷹野さんと富竹さんと私と
圭一(けいいち)君って男の子の４人で…
Takano-san, Tomitake-san, me,
and a boy named Keiichi-kun.
詩音さん今度はどう
けじめをつけられる気ですか？
Shion-san, how are you planning
to show responsibility this time?
う～ん…
奮発して爪５枚くらいいっとく？
How about tearing
off five fingernails?
ハァ…ごめん
I'm sorry.
But I grew up in Okinomiya
because Granny hated me...
でもさ私鬼ばばに嫌われて
ずっと興宮育ちだし
学園に閉じ込められてて―
...and trapped in an academy, so
Hinamizawa isn't familiar to me.
雛見沢のことなんて
知らなかったから
Shion-san, I am on your side.
詩音さん
私は あなたの味方のつもりです
ですがいくら私でも
かばいきれないこともあります
But there are things that
even I cannot stand up for.
葛西…
Kasai...
ア…アハハッ…
ごめんお姉が来たから切るね
Sorry, Sis is here,
so I have to go.
タハハッ…チェッ…まいったなぁ
Man.
Not good.
Calm down.
Why should I panic now?
落ち着け私…今更慌てたって…
If I act like Mion,
then Shion will disappear.
私が今みたいに魅音になれば
詩音は消える
Since I told him Shion
entered the ritual tool shrine...
葛西に詩音が祭具殿に
入ったって伝えてあるから―
詩音はオヤシロさまのたたりで
鬼隠しに遭ったことになるだろう
...people will think that she was
spirited away by the demon.
残るは前原(まえばら)圭一のみ…
The only one left
would be Keiichi Maebara.
It might be a good chance
to lure the enemy.
敵を釣り上げるいいチャンスかも
圭ちゃん
悪いけど餌にさせてもらうね
Kei-chan, sorry,
but I'll use you as prey.
（詩音）前原圭一が
ある日突然いなくなった
Keiichi Maebara suddenly
disappeared one day.
…じゃ失敗
Then it failed.
敵が食いつく瞬間を
見逃さないよう注意しなくちゃ
I need to be careful not to miss
when the enemy latches on.
Kei-chan.
（詩音）圭ちゃん
（圭一）うん？
Mion, what's the matter?
魅音
どうしたんだ？調子悪そうだけど
You don't look good.
昨日お祭りで
親族の宴会に巻き込まれちゃってさ
I got caught up in
a family gathering yesterday.
And had some...
それでチョイッと
二日酔いかよ　年いくつだ？お前
A hangover? How old are you?
アハハッ…勘弁してよ
体調悪いのは本当なんだからさ
Leave me alone.
I'm really not feeling well.
Oh, yeah. Kei-chan.
ああそうそう圭ちゃん
（圭一）うん？
Did you see Tomitake-san
and Takano-san last night?
昨日の晩さ富竹さんと
鷹野さんに会わなかった？
さ…さあどうかな…
I-I don't know.
He sucks at acting and lying.
ウソも演技も最低レベル
（詩音）
そう　じゃもうひとつ質問ね
I see.
Then I have another question.
同じく
ゆうべ詩音に会わなかった？
Similarly yesterday,
did you see Shion?
Didn't you ask that yesterday?
（圭一）それ昨日も聞いた
Did I?
そうだっけ？
Then that means
Mion asked him?
…てことは
魅音が聞いたってこと？
ゆうべ？くそ！
Last night?
Damn, when I asked her...
私が問い詰めたときは―
“祭具殿に入ったことなんて
知らなかった”なんて言ったくせに
...she said she didn't know about
us entering the ritual tool shrine.
でも誰とも会ってないなら良かった
Well, I'm glad
you didn't see anyone.
Oh, I thought I might get
a different answer if I asked again.
あっいや…
また改めて聞いたら違う答えが
返ってくるかなって思ってさ
Then I'll let them know that you
weren't involved in anything bad.
私 言っとくね “圭ちゃんは 何も
悪いことには加わってない”って
みんなに
ちゃんと言っておくからね
I'll tell everyone.
あっ…“みんな”って？
Everyone?
フフッ…これで圭ちゃんには
不信感と危機感を植え付けたはず
Now I've seeded
Kei-chan with doubt and fear.
But look at the way he reacted.
だけどあのうろたえ方ったら…
今度は詩音に戻って
圭ちゃんを見張ってやろうかな？
Now I'll be Shion and
keep an eye on him.
Oh? Mion-chan?
（公由）あれ？魅音ちゃんかい？
Well, everyone...
（牧野(まきの)）そんでは皆さん
...thank you for gathering
despite your busy schedules.
本日はお忙しい中
お集まりいただき恐縮です
We'll begin first with the
village headman's greeting.
あ～初めに
村長からご挨拶をいただきます
Village headman, please.
村長どんぞ
え～座ったままで失礼します
Forgive me for remaining seated.
（公由）え～まず…
The village headman's
greeting was long and boring.
（詩音）
村長の挨拶は長くて退屈だった
だが５年前の―
But when he started to talk about
the serial mysterious deaths...
雛見沢連続怪死事件の
説明が始まると―
...from five years ago,
the room became silent.
空気がしんと重く沈み込んだ
Mion-chan,
did Oryo-san say anything?
魅音ちゃん
お魎さんは何か言ってたかい？
園崎家当主代行園崎魅音です
I am Mion Sonozaki, the
Sonozaki head's representative.
本日は当主お魎に代わりまして
出席させていただきました
I came today in place
of the head, Oryo.
I'll be fine.
大丈夫
"That" is inside me too
because we're twins.
あれは私の中にもある
私たちは双子なのだから
Unfortunately,
Oyashiro-sama's curse...
不幸にして
オヤシロさまのたたりは―
...has occurred for
the fifth year in a row.
５年目にも
下されることになりました
大変悲しいことです
This is quite depressing.
Does anyone know why the
curse occurred again this year?
どうして今年もたたりがあったか
分かる人はいますか？
（役員たち）いや…
Yes, it's because the ritual tool
shrine's taboo was broken...
そう 祭具殿の禁を犯し
土足で聖域を踏み荒らして
汚(けが)れを持ち込んだからです
...with shoes invading the holy
ground and bringing impurity.
（どよめき）
（役員１）祭具殿に？
なんちゅうことを！
What's that?
（役員２）あほんだれが！
Those fools!
Those cursed fools!
バチ当たりどもが！
Even the usually
calm Kimiyoshi?
いつもは
優しい公由のおじいちゃんまでが…
（詩音）間違いない
There's no mistake.
The person who links Granny
and Oyashiro-sama's curse...
鬼ばばとオヤシロさまのたたりを
つなぐ人間が…
The person who conveys her
hidden intention is in this room.
鬼ばばの影の意向を取り次ぐ人間が
今この場所にいる！
I ask for silence.
お静かに願います
（公由）ほら静かに静かに
Come now. Silence, silence.
祭具殿に忍び込んだ賊は４人
あと２人います
Four thieves snuck into the ritual
tool shrine. There are two more.
その２人の狼藉者(ろうぜきもの)は
園崎詩音そして前原圭一
Those two violators are Shion
Sonozaki and Keiichi Maebara.
Shion Sonozaki has been...
園崎詩音は既にこちら…
Everyone was frighteningly
apathetic and emotionless.
（詩音）みんな恐ろしいほどに
無機質無感情だった
What about the other,
Keiichi Maebara?
もう１人の前原圭一は…
ハッ…まだです
Not yet.
Um, can you stop by my house?
（役員３）あ～じゃ
まあそういうことでよろしく
（詩音）あの…
家(うち)に寄ってもらえませんか？
（公由）
お魎さんが呼んでるのかい？
Is Oryo-san calling me?
Yes, it seems she wants
to tell you something in person.
はい　直接会って
話したいことがあるとか
Granny said she'll
change and come here.
（詩音）ばっちゃ
着替えてから来るそうです
Oh, that's fine.
I'll wait here patiently.
（公由）
ああいいよゆっくり待ってるから
I think it's about Shion.
多分
詩音のことじゃないかと思います
詩音ちゃんは今は？
（詩音）地下にいます
Shion-chan?
Where is she now?
In the basement.
そうかさすがにな祭具殿はな…
I see. Well, she did go
into the ritual tool shrine...
But I also feel sad for Shion.
でも
詩音もかわいそうかもしれません
ずっと
雛見沢から遠ざけられてきたんです
She's always been kept
away from Hinamizawa.
She must've
known it was wrong...
（詩音）いけないことだとは
思っていたでしょうが
...but she probably didn't
know it was a big deal.
そこまでとは
分かってなかったんじゃないかと…
魅音ちゃん
詩音ちゃんは反省してるんだろう？
Mion-chan, Shion-chan
is feeling sorry, isn't she?
Yes, but at this rate, she might
be spirited away by the demon...
（詩音）ええでもこのままじゃ
去年の北条(ほうじょう)悟史みたいに―
鬼隠しに
なっちゃうんじゃないかって…
...like Satoshi Hojo was last year.
Don't worry. As long
as Shion-chan is feeling sorry...
大丈夫！詩音ちゃんが
ちゃんと反省してるなら―
...she won't be spirited away
by the demon. Leave it to me.
鬼隠しになんかなるもんか
公由のおじいちゃんに任せなさい
あっ…本当ですか？
Really?
良かった　やっぱり公由の
おじいちゃんは味方だったんだ
Thank goodness.
Gramps Kimiyoshi
was on my side after all.
Unlike that cursed Hojo brat,
I'm sure she'll be forgiven.
バチ当たりな北条の坊主なら
いざ知らず
詩音ちゃんなら
きっと許してもらえるって
北条の坊主って…
Hojo brat?
北条の連中はしかたないさ
村を丸ごと売ろうとしたヤツらだ
We can't help the Hojo family.
They tried to sell the entire village.
It makes sense for
the entire family to be cursed.
一族郎党皆呪われて当然だよ
でもおじいちゃん悟史君は去年
詩音がけじめをつけたから―
But gramps,
I thought Satoshi's case...
...was overlooked since Shion
showed responsibility last year?
見逃してもらえることに
なったんじゃ？
Responsibility? For what?
けじめ？何の？
（詩音）ほら爪を３枚…
You know, the three nails.
Those three were for Kasai-san,
Yoshiro-san, and Shion-chan...
あれは葛西さん義郎(よしろう)さん
それから詩音ちゃんで―
...or so I heard.
３枚だって聞いてたよ
（詩音）ハッ…
It can't be.
そんな…
３枚目は悟史君じゃないの？
The third nail wasn't
for Satoshi-kun?
それに…
And after that, Mion came and
said everything would be forgiven.
そのあとに魅音が来て言ったよ
“あれで
全部許してもらえた”って
I wonder why Satoshi Hojo had
to be spirited away by the demon.
どうして北条悟史君は―
鬼隠しに遭ったのでしょう？
（公由）ええっ？
（詩音）悟史君のご両親は
確かに村を売ろうとしました
Satoshi-kun's parents
did try to sell the village.
でも悟史君にはどんな罪が？
But what sin did he commit?
聞かずとも分かります
御三家がそう決めたのです
I don't need to even ask.
The three great families decided it.
N-No, Mion-chan.
い…いや魅音ちゃん…
（詩音）“北条家なら―”
The Hojos are cursed
no matter what.
“何があってもたたり”
（公由）ハッ…
“北条家なら
何があろうと知ったことではない”
They don't care what
happens to the Hojos.
The Hojos are filthy.
“北条家ならば汚らわしい”
そういう考えが蔓延(まんえん)し
That type of thinking spread
and infected everyone's thoughts.
汚れた思考に汚染された
お前のような存在が許せない
I cannot forgive your existence.
お前のようなヤツが
悟史君一家を追い詰めて
People like you accused his
family and blamed them so.
あんなに…悟史君がかわいそう
I feel so bad for him.
What did he do?
何をしたの？何もしてない
He didn't do anything. He was
just part of the Hojo family.
（詩音）ただ北条家であっただけ
Then why?
なのにどうしてたたりが…
呪いが降りかからねばならないの？
Why did the curse, the spell,
have to fall upon him?
What sin did
Satoshi-kun commit?
悟史君に
何の罪があったというのか？
To get my happiness,
I had done everything...
...but had done nothing
to be blamed and accused of.
The sound of footsteps
became louder every day.
Then I noticed the fact
there was no time.
I was a believer in life,
to be myself always.
And was asking
whether I would be alive.
Give me a reason
why not to adopt in this way.
Or judge me to be guilty
of so many incurable sins.
Tell me why or why not?
Complaining way too much.
Maybe I overlooked
something fatal for me.
Preview
What you touched
is the wavering image.
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）触れたのは揺らぐ面影
What resounds
is the echo of sadness.
響くのは悲しみのこだま
What you smell
is your burnt memories.
香るのは焼けた思い出
When They Cry.
「ひぐらしのなく頃に」
"Eye Opening" Chapter,
Episode 5: COLD HANDS.
- "Eye Opening" Chapter -
Episode 05: COLD HANDS
"Eye Opening" Chapter,
Episode 5: COLD HANDS.
あなたは信じられますか？
- "Eye Opening" Chapter -
Episode 05: COLD HANDS
Can you believe it?